

PROFILE

I am a driven data scientist, data engineer, AI researcher and robotics developer. Programming and working with computers in general has been a passion for quite some time.

In love with automation and minimizing repetitive work, which is why I'm able to focus on efficient & application-oriented learning, developing and problem solving.

Switching views, working on agile projects and changing approaches often motivate me to study new topics, tackle hard challenges and deliver results.

BIRTHDATE 11 januari 2000

ADDRESS

Houthalen-Helchteren, Belgium

PHONE NUMBER +32486539354

MAILING ADDRESS kobethuwis26@gmail.com

KOBE THUWIS

EDUCATION

2018-2021: Hogeschool PXL

Bachelor in Applied Information Technology with a specialisation in Artificial Intelligence (AI) & robotics.

2012-2018: Kindsheid Jesu

High school diploma in Maths & Sciences

WORK EXPERIENCE

InfoFarm: Junior data engineer/data scientist 2021 - Present The ANPR Big Data Platform is a scalable and extensible platform for collecting, storing and aggregating ANPR data. My task within the project is to construct a big data lake using AWS and make the data usable for analysis, reporting and future processing.

PXL Smart ICT: Research & Development Intern 2021

ArtiFISHal Intelligence is a twofold project, consisting of scenes made in Unity which illustrate several reinforcement learning techniques. Secondly, the project contains a simulation of a marine ecosystem which uses state of the art evolutionary algorithms.

Chiro Meulenberg: Head Monitor 2018 - Present

Strandbal: Event Manager 2018 - Present

Youth Council Member 2019 - Present

PORTFOLIO

https://kobethuwis.github.io/

Make sure to visit my portfolio to view any previous projects, skills and relevant experience!